they came in loud they came in wrong but baby i made them part of my song
they pop and rude with the same old script trying to porn bomb the
Flexing hate and fear but I got glitter nails and a crystal sphere Doug D talking like it's 1952
Racist rants. Yeah, I banned you too, but every troll that clicks my stream just feeds the fire and this mystic queen
Your trauma dunk don't trigger much, yeah
Keep watchin', keep that frown
Cause trolls make the world go round, down
JT and Reigns devilishly hot
If Lucifer had a twitch, they'd co-host a spy
Cute little demons with chaos in their eyes
But even they know not to cross these vibes
Then there's Alex, yelling, you're all the same
Dude's got more clones than a bad video game
I mute, I boot, I laugh so hard
While I shuffle my deck and pull your card
Droppin' porn like he's trying to destroy
But guess what, Psyche don't fold
You're just another name in the block-
I think Apollo gets it, though, like about why I do these.
One second.
I have one more.
Brand new hot off the press.
Well.
But if we have a dirty mind, it's because someone probably walked all over our brain with their nasty feet
Hold on
It's a strange
Transmission
The colors fell off the grid
no shape no sound just static whispering who i was before i logged in
when i'm near you time falls like that coat meaning deletes itself i forget my own
fantasy utopia
Again, and again, upload the story, start the sin
Neon baby, fascist fantasy, topia bleeds in binary
Neon baby, fascist fantasy, heaven's gotta fight
and taught me doubt.
Utopia, the dream they sold us in grayscale.
Utopia, a mirror that erases your face still.
mirrored this one. One more, then I'll be here to talk once again.
Slash where it
that has Irish cream in it. Don't drink that. Coffee and Irish cream.
It's so loving.
You're so perfect.
Babe.
You just give kisses?
Oh Daryl shut up
We're emotional beings, so how can we not dwell on them?
What, we're going to be like robots?
Hey, dude.
I'm sorry, I don't need to.
Hi, baby.
Did you hear her purr?
You know
You know like black cats are actually like more like a red you can't see it in her
Yeah, my little my guardian
They are
Especially like my cat's in some of your lap
Oh my god, my camera looks like my webcam is like a cyclops
Can't show it on this
Do you think you know
Yeah, and then and they they don't expect that they like bested. They don't judge like they just like love. Oh
She loves me
You see
Hmm people think they know so much, huh?
People really don't know very much. I think they do
So we're very about like appearances or what something looks like
Just like was that really what it is
No, no says a peepee something like that
Means it's not a pipe and it's like there's a picture of a pipe, right?
And it says, this is not a pipe, because what you're seeing
actually is a picture of a pipe.
It's a representation of something.
But it's not a pipe itself.
It's a picture of a pipe.
Just a picture.
I do kind of like the quote.
Those that think they know everything
are really annoying to those of us that actually do.
No, I don't I don't know everything
But uh, I know enough
But it's like that's the fun is like
Know thyself with Apollo here, he knows know thyself
Soccer cheese, right? No thyself and you will
You will know God or something like that
Oh, that's sweet.
But anyway, so my cat Pie was here last night.
I heard Tricks growling.
I was like, and it's, he growls.
It's like, it's like a, it's not,
people are like, oh, cats don't growl.
He was growling.
And so I was like, there's somebody,
or something inside the house.
And then I looked and there's a black cat.
And I was like, oh, it's Lenore.
And then I looked and then Lenore was sitting over there.
Now they're gonna look closer. I was like, oh my gosh, it was my cat pie
He's been gone for over a year and he's all big and muscular and he has a little bit of
White on his chest tux had like a more of a more of a white on his chest
I just had a little bit of white on his chest
But I had two black cats not littered their tricks his brothers
But they took off their boy, you know, they're all boys except for one girl
But he was he was fat. He looks and he just came in and then he he walked by he rubbed against me
Then he ran back out and probably be gone for another year
But it was good to
See my baby
Human beings are stubborn people.
So let me see.
Why'd I come here?
Why'd I come back?
I guess it's not easy being so receptive.
If you look into, there's something called human design.
You can look into it if you've never heard of it.
This guy named raw like he doesn't renamed himself raw
I think he went to a visa and like did a lot of mushrooms or something like that
He came up with this whole system
It's pretty cool. I can actually bring it up
And it's called human design it goes into like the chakras. I need to download it
Goes into and it goes into like a type. I can tell you a little bit about
Well, if you want me to go into you, I can tell you about you, but
Or anybody here because I do want to go more into like astrology with people
Plus the music. I'm gonna really plan on doing a lot more music
Like it's cut it's like a lot
Like constantly
The ideas, okay human design
You can you can see kind of like how it okay, so here it is human design app actually have it installed, okay
So it's a little bit more complicated than astrology.
Let me see.
I'll tell you what it says.
It says, human design is,
it's really interesting.
Okay, well, anyway, this is what the chart
will look like right there.
Okay.
And when you see my chart, you'll see like when it's like not filled in, oops, when it's like when they're clear, that means like you're receptive.
Oh, wow. And we're gonna, so right now these are clear, like the two, the two on the top.
Those both wide open which is like good for a psychic, but it also means like a lot of
Things that come into my mind are not from me they're just I receive I'm like a huge I'm like a very receptive that makes me a good psychic but
And some people disagree with that but I'm not
Everybody's up tea, but let me see okay, so
Yeah, it was really bad today like um, you know, I had like 10 scrap people people are coming looking for scrap metal and stuff
Okay, one second
But then like the sad part was that the guys like oh well your dad
I talked to your dad and my dad passed away last year. So I was like well my dad's you know passed away
Right here. He's like oh, I'm sorry. And he's like well. He says his name is Alexander Bates
Anyway, I
Charity saved
Okay, so just like I said, so this is my human design chart.
This chart, the table shows the human design calculation
at your time of birth.
The numbers represented are all defined
I Ching gates in your chart.
A gate is defined when a planet
or a sun is positioned to them.
Okay, so gate, that would be like,
if you have a house on the regular astrology chart,
that'd be if there's a planet in it
or it's like your sun sign.
And so then it goes into like it has these two call
I mean, it's like a little bit more complicated
But this column the black one is actually like based on a few months before you're born because that's considered like a conception stage and then
Or sorry, the yeah the the black ones are your birth and the red ones are a few months before you're born
So it's 88 days.
These are the design traits you are not aware of,
which other people see in you
and are new energies you came here to experience.
The most important gates are the sun, earth, moon,
north node and south node.
So in astrology, that would be Capricorn.
What would the earth be?
Well, my earth is,
Also Capricorn, that's the rising sign, right?
And then the North note is Leo, South note is Aquarius.
Moon is Aquarius.
I don't know why moon is not that important here, but.
Okay.
And so, it has all these gates and stuff.
I mean, it's like too complicated
to like really explain perfectly to you.
But basically this is like your body, right?
And they represent different organs, right?
Comes in this shape right and so there's different and there's different channels
And so there's gonna be like these channels that are filled in that connect and they're all different for everybody, right?
So we're gonna have these to find channels so I can look at my so it says I'm a projector. There's different types. There's like
There's like a manifestor
projector
And so projector
They have a good explanation of it projector
Basically, it's somebody that projects out the,
it projects out the experience, right?
And so it says, I'm a projector.
It says, my theme is success
and with the shadow side of bitterness.
And it says, I should wait for an invitation.
It does tell you interesting things about
Should you like be
Should you be proactive and they'd be doing things or should you wait for things to come to me? So I'm
According to my chart
It should be waiting for invitations.
So it says your natural guide, organizer and leader,
you're here to be recognized for who you are
and to help guide the other energy types
in the most efficient way.
As people around you are buzzing with energy and ideas,
you're able to understand them better
than they can understand themselves.
You have a deep and penetrating aura,
which allows you to hone in
and ask the deep and insightful questions.
Since you don't have your own energy, okay,
Most of my energy is received, right?
And so if the energy's not coming in,
I get very tired, lethargic.
It says, you need other people to feel successful, right?
Your goal is to find people who recognize your gifts
and welcome them.
You probably try to force your opinions and advice
on others since you see things they don't.
If you do that, you typically feel a backlash
and then end up bitter.
That doesn't mean you have to wait for others
to invite you all the time.
You can also ask for an invitation.
I have a better idea, which you would like me to share it.
Follow your authority.
And if you feel the opportunity is good for you,
offer guiding gifts.
That's also why I don't say, do you want to share a reading?
I would like, you know, really on top of people.
You know, sometimes I do, but for the most part,
I wait for them to ask, right?
Says, you are running on other people's energy, right?
Says, notice that the energy you feel
is not the energy of the people around you.
Sorry is the energy of the people around you and not yours you have to allow yourself time and space to relax and disengage
Go to bed. Oh
Sorry, okay, yeah, go to bed and
Okay
Go to bed and
An hour earlier than when you think you will fall asleep, okay?
I won't go into too much more, but I will tell you
It comes up with these numbers three five and you can be like a it's like one through five
So you're gonna be one number on the left chart one number on the right chart
so
my birth
I'm a three which is a martyr
and then
My subconscious is a heretic. Okay, so it says bumping into others at the conscious level learning from mistakes
At the subconscious level you are only valued if your solutions are practical wisdom through experience the theme
So the third line people are experimental
and experiential in nature.
You are bound to make mistakes, bump into the wrong people
and get stuck in the wrong situation.
You learn from your mistakes, you constantly ask yourself,
how did that affect me?
Thus internalizing the results.
You can't rely on someone else's experience to understand something. You must try it to know it.
Words are not powerful. Words are not enough for you due to your inward focus.
You can't just watch someone else do it, but need to experience it so you know it and live it.
So, fifth line people, which is the heretic,
are excellent interpersonal skills. You are the ruling line, however. Others don't see you as such.
Others see in you what they want to see father lover worker, etc
You can influence people. You don't know strangers. You are under pressure to have the right information
You must learn something practical and be able to tell others about it
Okay, so it goes into a lot of stuff, but I will tell you my planets
My my son, okay, so so the son it says I'm gate 54. It says so so this is important for me
It says marriage ambition
And then it says line three.
So it's gonna say like 54 is the gate
and then it's gonna say line three, so 54.3.
The line three, it says covert interaction exaltive, okay?
Which is an exaltive position.
It says the drive to rise above your circumstances
and create success through meaningful partnerships
is central to this gate.
You are ambitious and seek
Progress through collaboration. Embracing your desire for partnership allows you to align your ambitions with those of others,
creating mutual success.
If fear governs, you may become overly focused on personal gain hindering your collaborative efforts.
Okay.
So now my earth is, my earth is gate 53, three.
So that says development and beginnings,
line three, practicality.
The spark that initiates new cycles of growth
defines this gate.
You bring momentum to new projects
and experiences helping things begin at the right moment.
Embracing your role as a catalyst for new beginnings
allows you to set things in motion and create opportunities.
If fear governs, you may hold back
and missing the right moments to act.
Okay.
But I do understand I'm a catalyst for sure
Moon it says decrease and contraction the line to caution. It's in detriment. So my moon is kind of negative, right?
The spark of imagination that drives new experiences at the core of this gate.
You dream of what could be and wait for the right moment to bring those dreams into form.
Embracing contraction allows your vision to unfold when the timing is right.
If fear governs, you may be pressured to act before the moment is right, stalling your creative progress.
Okay, then we go to North Node, which is Leo.
Gate 33, Retreat and Privacy.
And then line four, dignity.
So in retreat and privacy, I gain energy.
Actually, it's good, okay?
It's a dignified, okay, so the need for time alone
and process experiences and integrate lessons
is key to this gate.
You carry the stories of the past
and share them with wisdom when the time is right.
Embracing your need for retreat allows you to reflect
and make sense of your experiences.
Very hermit energy if fear governs your experience you may
Resist the solitude feeling disconnected in your own wisdom. Okay, and then we go south node
Approach and sensitivity line for the team player. That's a quick sequerious. The query is all about teams, right?
The sensitivity to the needs of others, often sensing what they require before they even express it, is central to this gate.
Your presence creates emotional intimacy, fostering deep connections with those around you.
By tuning into others' needs and offering support, you create meaningful relationships.
If fear leads, you might be overwhelmed by others' emotions leading to burnout or disconnect from your true self.
Okay, so I need to be more in that individual energy
because when I get in too much of the Aquarius energy
with my South Node and also my Moon,
which is also an investment, right?
I get swept up in the energy of others
into the, because that's what Aquarius is.
It's all the connection with everything, the air, right?
Anyway, what else do I got?
I got Mercury, it says gate 61, inner truth, mystery.
Line one, occult knowledge, the pressure to seek deeper truths and mysteries of life to find the gate.
You are here to explore the unknown and find personal insights often in moments of silence and introspection.
Embracing your curiosity allows you to seek out the hidden truths that others may overlook. If fear governs, you may be overwhelmed by
uncertainty hindering your pursuit of truth.
Well, I'll do one more. I'll look at my Venus.
My Venus is gate 11, peace, ideas,
line three, the realist, which is detrimental, right?
The flow of inspiration and ideas
that bring clarity and insight,
you hold a vast library of ideas
waiting for the right moment to share them.
And I do have a whole library to share with you guys.
I bring out this a little bit at a time.
Trust that when it's shared at the right time,
your insights bring mental clarity
and offer practical solutions.
If fear dominates, you may hesitate to share your ideas doubting their value or feeling fearing they'll be rejected
Anyway, and I'll tell you about the martyr heretic
Which is I'm a 3-5 martyr heretic
Bumping into others at the conscious level learning from mistakes at the subconscious level
You are only valued if your solutions are practical wisdom through experience the theme third line people are
experimental and experiential in nature
I have read that already
I'm sorry if you
Hopefully you found that interesting, but I will go and I can do your human design if you want
It's basically you just see the same information as on your birth chart, but it just gives you a
An astrology is like in itself
Enough. It's a lifelong study
Does this complicate it to an excessive degree
Not for people like me
who are just very into like knowing everything like learning everything, right?
but um
It it can be a little bit technical, but I would tell you it is very I
studied it very like a lot several years ago and
It is very helpful, especially the part waiting for invitation and not like
Forcing myself
My beliefs are that stuff on the others. That's why it's good to have this platform
It's because people can kind of like come to me
And so they're already like they're looking for maybe what I have and then maybe they have what I'm looking for too. I mean
Life is about that sometimes but
Hey
So, do you find it interesting? Let me look at this chat. Let me see what's going on.
Let's see. The Lord knows I'm stubborn, but hey, nice to represent yourself around me.
Hold on. Lenore, okay. You think the cat has seen, thing that is inside, that thing that controls you?
Thing that is don't control me. You may have controlled Joe Shipley.
the chatter asked really, right?
And that's why Alexandra is right.
I mean, and people can say, oh, she, you know,
it's reaching, he's not this mastermind,
warlock, whatever.
Well, we put things in these terms, right?
I'll say what thing that is, and if you're in the chat,
I'm not trying to call you out or say anything negative.
But I'm saying you're that observer
That is very loud observer like I can I can hear you observing like I can because I'm so receptive I hear
So I do hear some stuff
I'm very careful about what I internalize though you afraid
Of the dark and my Empress
Can't receive email hey Canada dry
Wonder what's going on with sticky with an email
Your farts brother, okay, party brother. Oh, yeah, yeah, Canada dry, right?
Yeah, let's see
Hey, hello, okay, so
What's going on nothing's wrong? I'm cool. What's going on is like
I'm just very, I just feel like the negative,
I feel negativity like really keenly.
And it's like, I'm always feeling like this like judgment,
but it's like, and I, and I feel like people think
they understand me better than I understand myself.
And I don't understand myself.
Like it's like, I mean, it's a process, right?
And we all, and so it's like,
how can they understand me better than I understand myself?
If they're not me like right like just like I would say I would never say I know you better than you know yourself
Or I know more about it like
That's like and I wouldn't want to if I could have access to your
Web history and you know, we're have a camera on you 24-7
What is that
Nothing because can I see your heart I can feel it I can I can feel hearts
Do I see it? Do I know?
Do I know? No, I just don't understand how people think they can know me based on
Whatever, but it's like this constant
Constantly these inside jokes that I've never a part of right, but it's like I am I am the inside joke
Makes sense, right? I am the joke
But I'm not included in the laughter. It's like I'm just laughed at right. I don't know. Maybe I'm
Overthinking it, right, but I'm a thinker. I got this first house Mercury
Which is like
That's part of my identity is having this like crazy fast movie very changeable mind
Ups and downs and stuff. Plus Mars in the first house, Moon in the first house, Sun in the first house.
Capricorn Aquarius, first house. These are very opposite energies.
Capricorn is about the earth and the ground in this.
and materialism and what you see.
And then individualism and then the Aquarius
is about the collective.
And I'm really trying to get out of the collective
into my North node energy, which is Leo.
Leo is the individual, Leo is the lion, it's the sun.
The sun is like the leader, right?
But you can see it's easy for me to go into like the
Collective energy like the like when I go backstage and stuff, and I'm just like backstage
It says my energy mixes with everybody else's and it's like I can just like
Who I'm not being I'm not the center of attention, but I'm supposed to be the center of attention
I'm kind of going on about my own astrology, but if you guys
Are you just said I'm pretty good at going over other people's I don't know but it seems like
nobody's really interested in that and it's like I don't know maybe it's hard I really can
I really can't see things but I have the Cassandra complex
Cassandra was like this princess who Apollo fell in love with her Apollo the God of the Sun
He fell in love with Cassandra and then
in exchange for like her love
He made a deal. He's like, okay, I'll make you a prophetess. I'll give you this like
prophetic ability where everything you'll just know the future you'll know everything
I'll give you that ability and then in exchange for your love
She's like, okay, sure
And then she was like, ah, Paolo's kind of weird.
And she's scorned, she's spurned him, right?
And so Paolo's not really like, he's a son, right?
He doesn't really like to be spurned.
And so he basically spit in her mouth
and made it so everything that she spoke
Would be it would be prophetic. It would be true, but it would not be believed by anybody
And so she had the whole prophecy about the Trojan horse. Don't let that horse in the fucking
City do not open the gate. Do not let that horse in that horse is bad news
And no one believes her
They let the horse in we know what happened from there, right?
Oh, thank you, Spunky. I loved and I loved do I love doing that and I need to like
Sometimes I should be like
Promoting it more and now I eventually
will but like again I'm waiting for invitation I want people to like come to
me but yeah and I and I want to do I want to put that into your song I did
into a video for you and stuff too because if you get a report from me if I
have stuff to add to it I will plus I love adding like the art and the music
and stuff I think it has a whole different dimension I don't think anybody's
doing it like I would do it like I think it's like so unique
Working with things like AI, which I think AI is like
Basically able to leverage this and intelligence and I do consider it
To the artificial intelligence. That's like a misnomer. Okay. It's like
It's technology. Okay. It's a technology. It's a tool
Blended with the human
Emotion and the human guiding it it produces them. That's so that's why I
Think my music is
It's like I think it's really good, but I think it's like I think it is a form of divination as well
I'm of course, I'm a Chandler so thank you you're interested
Yeah, I mean I would love to do like you know, I'd love to do like a hour I can hour on the phone or on like a
zoom or
Skype or whatever and
Going through your chart with you and like the houses and like
and
There's so many there's so much that is useful and
Helpful, but it is like a lifelong study and it's like I've studied for years and years and still it's like I'm always coming up with like
Oh, yes, it's like, it keeps clicking, clicking, clicking.
So I know there's something to it.
I would, yeah, that would be awesome.
And, yeah, and I think it'd be great to,
great to, way to help people
and right, it's about knowing myself.
I'll pull a few cards.
From these sodacity deck. I have some audacity even thinking
That's why you know to be like on a pan a panel host or
On the internet or having even having your face out there
I'm not gonna say maybe narcissism is not a strong word
But I would say you have to have this like really high self-esteem or at least like
It's confidence like there's a confidence
And a little bit of audacity and saying, hey, listen to me.
Look at me.
I have something to say.
I do believe that.
Spongebob, OK, if I pull you a few cards, you're still there.
I'll pull some out of this deck.
Anybody else, too?
And I'll do free readings, of course.
I love the book.
OK.
I know.
But I do, what's that saying?
Bro, there's a song and it's like my problem is I care too much, right?
Okay
Okay, well you got the burn bridge, but this is in reverse
Okay, so there is like maybe a bridge that seemed like it was on fire, but it was saved
Or maybe like there's a a bridge that you thought was burned that wasn't quite
Wasn't quite
Okay, and so I don't know if this was like another opportunity in friendship or love or something like that
But I do and it's also number one too, it's the number one car, which is a magician I
Would say this burn bridge is
The charcoal, the charcoal's enough to keep it steady,
get you over the water and stuff.
The bridge is not burned.
Something didn't close, but that's not a bad thing
because firm bridges can be, you know,
if it's really, some bridges are meant to be burned,
but a lot of bridges are burned that we regret, right?
We have the high priestess. Okay, you oh and you of course have the high priestess energy and look it's like
She's like relaxing this bathtub
You know having little those little stokie or
Little weed you like the link Apollo sure
Yeah, just like that's about
being in touch with your inner self
having a
Knowing and inner knowing about things also being very receptive. Yes, I got the link for your poll. I'm sorry. I'm sorry a little bit
Slow right now. I am drinking like an Irish cream
You always get that card. I know we get the hype. I'm actually surrounded by high priestesses
Even like I would say my initials are you know usually in the high priestess card
It says JB on the pillars. They're the the Freemasonry pillars of Joaquin Boaz
Kabbalah Freemasonry
These these two pillars. There's a black pillar a white pillar the polarity that we sit between
But it's JB
JB is my initials, my dad's initials, my mom's initials.
Okay, but anyway.
Wow, so many high priestesses I've met in the past,
especially since I came here, it's fine, I'm like you.
Also, Emma had also a tattoo of the high priestess,
like you did, oh, here's Canada Dries coming up.
Hey, what's up?
Hey there.
Hi, here's Apollo.
Hi, Apollo.
Ooh, what's this?
That Apollo or no, look at that chest. Yes, it's me. It's me. It's me. It's me
Okay, good. I just have one more purpose. Yeah, good
Sorry, sorry. It's okay. Okay. Okay. Oh, yeah, spunky. We got we had the moon in reverse and so the moon in reverse
I would say actually like coming out of some kind of illusion
and
The something cycling through that you've seen they're now you're able to see the whole picture clear clearly
because usually the moon and regular is like about
illusion, deception, not really deception, but like a fantasy and you know how like
the moon and things are under this blue light. Hey, hey, what's up? Hi, you look
beautiful. How are you? Good, getting ready for work.
There you are. Oh, well, um, yeah, but uh, yeah, so this moon
Well, she's in this like she's in this desert to just desert with the give a dog. I do. Do you hear him?
Give it. Oh, you know, I
They're right here
Well the dogs sitting right next to you, too. There's a dog and
But the but I would bet since it came reverse I would say
It's like that. You've seen the whole cycle. You've seen you've seen everything
Everything you need to see in the cycle. So now you have the whole picture. That's what I see
It's like there's not there's not a confusion or illusion about it anymore. You have the whole picture. So you
Okay, you're like
And if you don't you will
You know, it's also the moon and she's kind of mooning the camera a little bit. You're right, so
Canada drive you like that one, okay
And I want to pull one from this...
There's one more deck for you.
This deck is more like a woman's deck.
My dog really wants to say hi to you.
Oh, oh yeah.
I love doggie.
This is this is a believe in your own magic deck. Well, I'll just put one card for you from this has a crown on this on the
On the outside of it. You got oh my gosh, so you got red it says red
It says forgive and look she's in the bath again with the flowers. It's just like the other the other part right here
Yeah, look she got like two of these bathtub card look it
Taking a spiritual bath I say or something like that or just like getting in touch with yourself in the bed
You love bats or something. Oh, yeah, I have a Japanese soaking tub
Okay
Is that true yeah, yeah, I do who is it who is she touching?
Who's she touching?
When in the car in the cards
You say there's a spiritual touch or something like this
Well, okay, so I mean it's it's like the high priestess in one and then this other one is as forgive and then there's
Looks like there's rose petals and stuff like that. Well, there's there's roses all over this one
There's rose petals in the other one. I'd say maybe incorporate some rose petals to or um
spiritual bath salt coffee and lemon juice really works wonders for like a spiritual bath
but anything you like to put in a bath baths are very very good to like you know having a hot so
it just like is like great so i like flour oils and a Himalayan salt um yeah the Himalayan salt is
Hi Canada dry
But also it's kind of interesting and the bathtub is on legs on both. They're like these bath tubs. That's cool
Yeah, so those are nice bath tubs. And so I would say definitely this is when you can get in touch
She's like a little bit more like she's smoking some a blunt right there
But then here's, but let's forgive. That's interesting. Okay. And she's like really considering something like maybe that's like the time to consider something that you've been thinking about forgiving, forgiving somebody.
Um, maybe, um, this is, I just see it's a, like, there's like a healing. There's like, there's like, uh,
good, high, good time to get in the high priestess interview for you. So I hope you like that.
Thanks, psyche.
And I'd love to yeah, I'd love to go into like I did you know
I did like some of your interesting placements and something to report, but I'd love to go more into
Your astrology with you, whatever you'd like
Yeah, there's so much interesting stuff you can learn so
How are you? How are we? We're all up at so it's four in the morning, right?
You did yeah
Are you saying good night or are you now you've decided just to hang out with us along well a
Couple questions. Can we do a trivia night again soon? We haven't done trivia in a long time
I feel like that really brings the people together
Yeah
Do you not like trivia night? I like trivia it kind of like what I was like, you know kind of like I
Kind of like beta and page. It was fun to do it with them and stuff
And now it's like, you know, well, Paige likes to come on still, but kind of like, I don't know, I'd love to, and it just makes me think of like, you know, kind of like more innocent times on the show before everything went to hell.
As long as it is without saying that it is, I'm okay with it.
Yeah, I mean, oh my gosh, he's in the chat. Oh my gosh, he's in the chat. Yeah, the thing that is, you know, he's a little bit of a know-it-all.
I like to be the one who's a know-it-all. And here he is, and he knows probably more of the trivia than I do. But I'm not bad, though.
Alright, Zach.
I mean, he's a walking Wikipedia.
Yeah, he is. I mean, it's that bald head. It absorbs those sun rays.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. See? Yeah, yeah.
The knowledge and so yeah, okay. Oh, I will plan a game night. I will plan a game night, you know, all right
Well, I just wanted to say good night. Thank you, Canada. I think you're coming up and thanks for being
my side
You know what and I want to apologize to your your girlfriend
I think I think ghost was just you know playing around, but I know it wasn't really that that cost some I
Apologize and it's like that. That's not like the
the energy I have, but, you know, or, or, or, you know what I mean?
I gotcha.
There's a lot of those around here.
Just let her not apologize.
I'm sorry.
Sleep tight.
Don't let the bugs bite.
Yeah, sleep tight, Canada.
Good night, guys.
Good night.
Yeah.
Yeah, I got these rings. I mean I got all these rings on team move. They're all you know, but I love these rings so much
Oh, they're cool
Yeah, and I got so much stuff. Oh, I got this thing too. You're look at this. Oh, I used to probably saw it
This didn't that's so cool. Yeah, I got this. It's a cane. It reminds me of like Jafar from a lot of
Yes, well, I was like well, I thought I was making out with it, but it is really like
Quality made. I mean, it's like, you know, it's really nice. Really. They have such good deals on that on that. They do
That's make staff. That is everything
Everything's from China pretty much anyway, right?
Where who is the sexy blonde gilf on the panel? Hold on a second. Oh, gilf
Do you mean me?
Me. Oh you oh
It's funky. I think I think you meant but yeah, mine's more. Oh, oh, yeah
Skeeter so tonight I went on beat is and I was like I put my name is vegan patriot
And I came on the way and she was like she's like I don't think that's vegan patriot
I just wanted to give her a giggle because I remember when I got the Speedos, I got them a little bit before 4th of July and I put them on and I went on her show before 4th of July and she just laughed and stuff like that even I think she was mad at me at that time and then we just made up for that so I thought it would be kind of funny but then she was like oh he didn't come up for me he came up for
Blogger no and then whatever that Victoria J. No, I did not come up for either of them
I came up for her, but it's okay like I I just kind of I'm gonna constantly be misunderstood and so
but I
Try I can only try so much, but it's like a it's like a constant push pull
Thing where we're just like we we make progress like a little bit and it's like oh, I love you and it's like and then it's like
She's like it's so hard
Relationships are really hard. I'm not good at them. I'm not I'm really not good. Oh, you're back to the text. Okay. I'm sorry
I didn't see I'm sorry here you go
I'm really bad at relationships.
That's why I've never really been in a one, like.
Good morning, everybody.
Good morning, Fingies.
Evening, Apollo.
There we go.
Calimera.
I miss Greece.
I love going to Greece.
Go on, I just wanted to come up.
It's easier to chat when you're actually on panel.
Talking, yeah.
Yeah, sometimes I think I talk too much, but.
I should be on panel. I like to be behind the scenes a little bit, too, though.
It was really hard tonight, actually. School of Athens, you know, you're a good guy.
Wow, you are a loudmouth. You are a loudmouth. You really annoyed the fuck out of me.
I came in when...
there was a giant fight between some New Yorkers.
Yeah, that was Alex in School of Athens, yeah.
Oh, it was the School of Athens, I don't know.
It was just like, I walked in and I walked out.
I was like, this is, wow.
Well, cause he just wouldn't stop talking.
I mean, it's a little, I don't know.
There was like some doxing and then some threats.
Oh yeah, and Alex, well, I find Alex 30 bucks
cause he doxed, he was like, he doxed easy.
Today and like so say does mom's name and stuff and then then yesterday he accidentally pornbomb me and so I
Just had to give him a little slap on the wrist like Ali cuz that's the only way he'll learn
Our things was actually over at the bloggers just now driving blogger nuts
Yeah, well blogger kind of drove me drives me nuts too, and it's like
I like blogger kind of but he has this like kind of like I have this clip on my shorts where he's like
Oh, well, you know, you have to be a humble, a humble person and like, you know, and I was like, he's acting like so holier than now, like, oh, he's just so above everything and I'm like this, like, just so, so unhumble and, you know, saying, no, I can be humble too.
I mean, is that we all have our moments. I just feel like when people get that ego with me, and then people think we look alike too, but.
Really?
Yeah, I don't think we do he's actually like five foot two or something like this like long hair. I guess
The long hair plus he's we say a lot of Botox. He has a
My my butthole is not as
Pro-labs. Are you psyche?
63. Oh man, you're real tall. I'm tall too for a girl at least
Five seven five eight five nine. Wow, that is very tall for
Yeah, well, that's great though. I
You know, I like being tall, but I
Don't know to tell people sometimes, you know, it's stereotypes about yeah
To be tall but when you get older and you're big, you know in high it's not that cool anymore
It's a lot to carry around
Well, and I'm a I'm a hundred and like 40 pounds and six three and so yikes, you can see like I'm
Tiny thing. Yeah, like long. I am like that might be a little
Psych honestly
Yeah, when I was a baby, I almost died when I was under a year old because I was not able
to keep food down, like any food, like I would projectile vomit everything and so that was
of course not very pleasant for my parents when I was just like projectile vomit everywhere,
but and then there is, and then the doctors thought that she was like munchausen by proxy
because they didn't really figure it out at that time.
But what was wrong, they had just figured out a couple years before.
The surgery for and stuff. So I was very lucky like a couple years before I wouldn't they wouldn't have survived
I was like I was really skinny and I was so skinny like I
Was blonde. I was so blonde that my hair was white
It's like I was bald, but I had no veins and so when I was in the hospital for the surgery
I think they had to put the IVs and the veins in the head and stuff like that
And so I've always been just like very, very skinny and like, but luckily like,
it's called pyloric stenosis, which is like a narrowing of esophagus.
And so that's what I was going to guess with the projectile vomiting. Yeah.
Yeah. And luckily, I think they just figure out in the late seventies or something like about
like the surgery for it. And so I was very lucky. And then also like I drank like,
and I was like three years old, I drank a bunch of floor cleaner.
My brother found me convulsing on the floor
Yeah, and here he ran me I got my stomach pumped from that and then fucking scary
Yeah, an older brother I assume
Yeah, my my my my I have two brothers
My mom my mom had two sons so one is like 12 years older than one is when it's 10 years older
so he was like 14 or 15 and he was like
He was the school was across the street and the police station the fire department was up the street
And so he found me he like ran me up the street and then
they got in the police car and then there was a big line of people picking up kids from school and
everything and they thought that he was getting arrested and stuff because he was kind of like a
bad kid but but no he's really saved my life and uh and he was so you know and so I just got lucky
a bunch of times we also had like um we have we had a pool you know and like a lot of we had some
animals die in the pool and like almost almost all of us almost drowned at some point or another
Huh, well, I know we had an African grape parrot that drowned in the pool
We've had the raccoons that had died in the pool
Well did not our pet not pet raccoons, but yeah, that's the saddest thing was we had this African grape parrot and it got chased off
Kind of like cage, you know, and it was very sad, but um
Yeah, and we had raccoons that was sometimes drowned in the pool. Actually my older brother David. He's my oldest brother. He um
There's a picture of him with the stomach and it has this big red ring on his stomach
Like and he had gotten stuck to the pool drain on the stomach and it was my god at the bottom of the pool
Yeah, it didn't have a cover on it at the time. So it's just a pool. Yeah
Killer fool. Yeah, and so all of us have fallen in and like, you know at one for another
So I'm very lucky. I am that I know have survived and
I've also been stabbed, you know, I was stabbed in the ear like 2018, yeah, 2018, I was stabbed
with like a sharp.
Object I thought it was I thought it was punched in the ear, but then it started bleeding
Yeah, it's like inside
Sorry, yeah, it's it was bad and uh, yeah
But I mean it was it was pretty bad because the guy that did it like a year later he like
came back, or he was like, you know, there was a restraining order against him, the police put it,
I didn't put it, but I still was like, I forgave him, I thought he was really cute.
Dude, I don't care how cute you are, you stab me in the ear.
Then he ended up unaliving my neighbor.
And then he got arrested, and then he hung himself in jail.
Yeah, and so I was very troubled soul to say the least.
And, yeah, hold on, hold on, who's this in the chat?
Just another, I don't know who this is,
I've never seen this person,
but I'm gonna bring him up, hold on, it looks interesting.
Who is this person?
Hey guys, we have a surprise guest right now.
I don't see anybody.
Is that Q, who is this?
My name is Jeff Garcher.
Okay.
Hello. Hello. Hello, my friend is Darryl.
Darryl. Hi, how are you?
What's it?
Too many beers too early, man. Fuckin'
Who is it Darryl Darryl Kotsek from okay, okay. Okay. Yeah, I know Darryl
Well, you're too dark. Anyway, good man. Good to see you come back
You had a couple of days to recoup yourself
You know, I've been on I've been on every day this year except for two days. I've streamed every single day this year
I've been very very consistent and
In a record that same pass
But I used to do 12 hour streams, I used to do like, you know, like when I, I would, I would just basically wake up, turn on the camera, be on camera all day, pass out drunk, and I would just drink every night, like six to 10 beers.
Now I just have like, I just finished off my bottle of...
Just had a little bit of this. Well, you went a while there without getting drunk on stream, right? Right?
Well, I'm not even drunk now. I just had like a I just put a little bit
You know what I mean without doing the trash thing getting trashed. Yeah, I um, yeah
But let's be honest think that it's let's be honest, okay when you get to trash every day
People trash talk about you
Involve you on any kind of straight come on
You need some some way to release it
I know
I'm just saying he still stopped getting trashed every day on stream
But not that much not that much anymore. Do you know that?
I had like a weird, I had a bad experience with the guy
That's what I'm saying, Apollo, are you not understanding? That's what I'm saying. He hasn't been
He's doing good
I'm trying to, I'm trying to
My bad, my bad
Go ahead
like when you were petting him was so cute yeah and uh miss lola i used to drink i could drink
like a 12 pack of corona and not be drunk i would just be like so i'd have to drink like voodoo
rangers and i have to drink like i would drink six of them or something i mean i can't have no idea
It's they're strong 8% alcohol now. I drink
Yeah, but they're big they're tall cans it's a tall can and it's like it's actually like a
Kind of a bitter. I think it's an IPA so it's kind of a bitter taste now
I like the drinking like the hurricane punch Mike's heart eliminate and I can just drink two of those and I'll be good and
so
We go through different I go through different phases. I plus I I smoked pot for 25 years
And then I quit last year for like six months and now I just like can like
Actually like go without it for a while. I still do like once in a while, but pot is uh
Yeah, wait, just an extra month
I just you know, it just doesn't get it with pot. Like it just puts me to sleep
Yeah, it gives me zombies man, but it can also there's calm and composure as well
and it's like it's just like a
Brepper freshers sometimes
You can also make people anxious as hell, you know
For the most part, I don't need to be calm down, I'm pretty chill, so yeah
Like it really does chill me out. It helps me sleep
Like if I have to do something during the day if I have to you know meet people or whatever
Yeah, I'd rather not be high. Yeah, I think you're just at home lounging. Yeah
I'm it makes me very kind of dumb like I started smoking pot in college and I was like the first year of college
when I started smoking pot
I failed like every, I was like, I was like,
You lost a few grand, Phil.
Shit.
Yeah, I like being sharp.
I do too, I do too.
And uh.
But, yeah, the fog is clear a little bit, but when I quit smoking, I would have the craziest nightmares, like the worst nightmares, but it's like, you can finally remember dreams and be...
So, that's nuts, eh? Yeah, I remember having that too. I stopped smoking weed for a long time.
They cannot block that, man.
Dreams came back, they were vivid, and they were fucking weird, man. Like, really weird.
Because weed, weed, uh, weed, uh, represses the, uh, represses...
Something like let me see but it represses your the deep sleep that the REM sleep
And so you don't sleep as deeply and so you that's why you wake up still tired when you smoke weed sometimes
Like all the weekend all things so to speak
Yeah, wait until you get a little bit older
Get sleep at all
Well, I love sleeping but it's like I I love
I just I like to sleep if I'm not in a good mood
That's like I just like want to like lay under the cover and you can see me do that sometimes on string
That's where I like hide out and get away from everyone
Yeah, but
Quite hi, but nation's dead
I mean, you know Lola brought in a big rat last night, didn't you?
Oh no.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
You're a president.
President.
And there's like, then I saw like a heart.
Like, oh.
Oh.
It's too much info, man.
Foxy.
Yeah.
The cat's bringing crazy stuff.
But, uh, and I told you my cat, Pie came back, like, after a year and he was just, he
looks all big.
I want a cat that did that.
Isn't that weird?
and you look at him and you're like, do I know you?
And then you're like, oh, shit, I do know you.
And then he like, and then I spilled him like,
come like rub against my leg a little bit
and then he ran out the house, right?
You know, and it's like,
I probably won't see him for another year
or if I see him in the video.
The same thing happened with my cat.
I never saw him again.
This was like five years ago and, and.
I don't know the check out the scene like to see oh are there are the other cats that I don't like still there
Because tricks was just like growling like you've never heard a cat. It just came back for its things
He was like who did all my cat there fuck this place
Yeah, he was looking he was interested. I hope he comes back
But yeah, he's his name was pie and he's like a black cat with like a little bit of white on his chest
But it was so sweet that he said goodbye like he came
I just felt him rub against my leg and then he just here and go out the little cat door
Hopefully he comes I do see it occasionally
It's good when you can resonate and connect with wildlife like that
You know, it's precious moments in it
animals all animals like I mean even the ones that you shouldn't go near they're freaking fascinating in their own way
Any of you have like what I have is like the kind of the snow white thing like
Yeah, like the things just like fly in front of me squirrels start circling the trees when I walk by I see butterflies I
Dogs always like love me cats will come up to me like
I had more than one cat come and give birth on my doorstep.
And I have my mom's homes and fix them
and send them off for a good life, like, yeah.
Yeah, I really have to trust you
because that's like, you know,
they'll look for the safest place, you know,
they'll really.
I feed the neighborhood cats that I'm sure my neighbors love me and then with that comes the raccoons too, so
Yeah
Possoms move into like under my couch
There's some baby possums like the mother came in and then like next day the babies came in and they would come out at night
I need the cat food. I had him for a couple of weeks and then it's like I had to evict them, but
Baby possums are cute. They are very cute. Yeah, the squirrels come in here play and stuff like that
I've also a headless squirrel one time
Yeah
Cats can do that perfect. He's the right thing, but he got our hand
You know, I mean he's right to curve a room, but you know, I mean only so much can take on
Yeah, I don't like how they pooped under the couch and stuff, you know, but so
In California they what armadillos armadillos, I haven't seen one, but
We do have like, you know, we have coyotes in the neighborhood. We have
Squirrels, I've seen a rat. I've seen rabbits around here
We have monarch butterflies and other like some really cool yellow butterflies like fluorescent yellow. I've seen black butterflies like
But do you ever see like Nicole Kidman has a quote and she says
She's like there's one like thing that really creeps me out and she's like butterflies
She's like butterflies early. She's like they're creepy to her
I
Think they're beautiful
But if you really like hold one and like really look at it, they do look wild
I got a little kit of Monarch butterflies from like a discovery channel or something like that
And it's like a little like net and then you it comes with it the little
Cocoon's and then they hatch and butterflies and then you flower in your house for a few days and they live a very short time
But I would recommend like watch it like if you could see like the whole process of like
Actually, they come as worms seen that when you see his worms
They spit themselves in the cocoon and then they come out as a butterfly and that's this thing
Yeah, and then psyche actually means butterfly. It's actually yeah, like he means butterfly or
Psyche also means soul like the soul of spirit in Greek. Hey Apollo, you know that like a psyche in Greek
Isn't it mean butterfly?
I will get the feeling that people said don't let don't let them mess with your side. I don't think maybe in old Greek, but in modern in modern greek
Well, let me look at Chris K is in chat just letting you know hey Chris K want to come up Chris K
I saw I've been trying to catch Chris K streams and stuff like that come on up Chris K
I gotta go to work so have a good day
Okay, so we are you have a great day
I'm gonna put I'm gonna put a the link in a Chris K wants to come up. He's always
There yeah, yeah, yeah on roads is it never
Was it roads or plot most so I can't recall which one
Roads or pop moves. I think it was roads honestly, but the loo these
Oh, maybe butterflies or something like that. Mm-hmm. It says psyche. Okay, so it says psyche Greek goddess. It says
Greek name, I don't know Paul if you can see this. Let me put it up on the screen. Oh, it's a good thing Greek
Where's my mouse? Okay, here we go. Yeah, please educate me, please
He dropped
Sorry about that.
Have a good time, man.
Derek, can you see that?
Yeah.
See he looks like a candle to you.
See he means soul.
Yeah.
And it says, oh, it says soul.
Psyche, yeah, Psyche, okay so it says, ah, yeah, now I see what you mean, Psyche, yeah and all that kind of like that kind of thing, yeah, okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, I see what you mean, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
She was once a mortal princess whose extraordinary beauty earned the ire of Aphrodite, Roman Venus,
when men began turning their worship away from the goddess towards the girl.
Aphrodite commanded Eros, makes Psyche fall in love with the most hideous of men, but the god
instead fell in love and carried her off to his hidden palace. Eros hid his true identity
and told Psyche that she must never gaze upon his face. Her jealous sisters
However, tricked her into disobeying, and the angry God foresuck her.
Psyche all searched the world for her lost love, and eventually came into the service
of Aphrodite.
The goddess commanded her to perform a series of seemingly impossible tasks, which culminated
in a journey to the underworld.
Psyche was afterwards reunited with Eros, and the couple were married in a ceremony
attended by the gods.
in the company of her husband, Eros, sometimes a pair of CK, or PSY, P-Y-S-K-H-A-I, CK were depicted,
the second perhaps representing the daughter, Hedone, which means pleasure, so they had a daughter.
Let me tell you this seriously, this true God's ideology, it's all about gangbanging.
You know how many... you know how many... you know how many white zoos had?
He was cheating. He was cheating.
Hey, hey, hey there.
Like a motherfucker.
About 500 women.
Plus he would turn into animals and so it'd be like bestiality too, right?
Oh, we're not about that, like, fuck it, no.
Lita and the swan, Lita and the swan, we also have, what else?
He turned Aya into a cow.
He turned them into animals so Hera wouldn't find them and stuff,
but then Hera figured out that Aya was a cow
and she turned into a gadfly to sting her until she...
Exactly.
And then she became these girls were pretty jam-walled on.
Into breathing.
It was all about it. It's a formal seriously. It was a formal
Then they need left and right
Right, and they also had like this, um, you know, they had something called the um, though the sacred order of thieves
It was the strongest army in ancient Greece, I believe and it was um
It was based on
Who's that God? I mean it was he was not he was not a God. He was a mortal. He was a mortal man
Oh, yeah Achilles, but um cuz
Right he had a male lover and they had a very strong bond
And so they figured that the strongest army would be of male lovers
So they had 150 150 male same-sex couples
It's a secret order of thieves, T-H-E-B-E-S, yes.
Thank God. Thank God. We don't have it anymore. Oh, my goodness. They were the bus. They're the most powerful army because
It's not my thing not your thing, but it's true
I know it's true. I know
With the gay army
Can you imagine, all these warriors standing against you, you know, dressed in pink, you know, and then hi-tai-tai.
Chris K says hello to Abraham Lincoln and Chris K.
is linking cute
Hey, I look like a linking when I had my I had my beard like just like strong. Oh my god
Literally everyone in my chat would come and say you look like a link in and then I go to the petco
I'm lady's like, you know, you look like Abraham Lincoln
You see the top hat when I shaved and all of a sudden I was autistic Wolverine. That's a compliment
Yeah, he was just a looking guy. He was very tall as well. I think he was six five
He also had a
His lawyer he slept in the same bed as his lawyer. He shared a bed. I'm his male lawyer, you know, I'm Lincoln
So there's rumors that he was gay, but I
Don't quite know also John Wilkes Booth. I believe I
Have theory that John Wilkes Booth is Edgar Allen Poe. He survived
You can compare the photos and actually if you look at if you look up John Wilkes Booth
He was a really interesting photo. He was actually, you know, his family was in the theater, right?
He was an actor, right? We know John Wilkes was an actor, but here's a picture of his
Oh, okay, here. Well, here he is a very good-looking guy right there John Wilkes booze right there
We're very dashing, but here's a picture of him with his brothers and the play. Let me see if I have this picture here
Yeah, they do
Just like Romans. Okay. It was this this was both of his brothers Edward and Judean junior in Julius Caesar
So interesting
Which one was
Almost booth left to right
Booth was on the left
He's like I right there. Yeah
And then his brother is right there
His brother they link him to and you're looking comfortable
Well, they're wearing togas and stuff and handles those are hard to hard to lace up, you know
Yeah, but he was uh
Let's say it says he performed with his brothers Everett and juniors in a single engagement production of Julius Caesar at the Winter Garden Theatre in New York
He played Mark Anthony his brother Edwin has the larger role of Brutus and a performance acclaimed as the greatest theatrical event in New York history
The proceeds went towards a statue of William Shakespeare for Central Park, which still stands today
Not interesting. Yeah
Shakespeare too
Do you think Shakespeare who's a man? You know Shakespeare?
For all of his brilliance he didn't teach his daughter daughters how to read his daughters were illiterate and sign their name with an X
And he did sign in his name with an X as well to a lot of the time
Isn't there some controversy if to as to whether Shakespeare?
Actually existed right well because he was writing about these royal like Italy
He was writing about all these all these like royal things around the Europe
And he knew you had this great knowledge of the opinion areas
Yeah, and how would he know this if he was just from this like little place?
He never really traveled or anything as far as I know like I think I think that
Shakespeare is actually the same group that
is the king james by the sea ancient and got good information of royal people
right but it's like where people really travel like like you know that's royal people right
it means it was he really i don't even know if he was really part of the court elizabeth's court
like um i do know that about john d if you are you familiar with john d
Never I didn't want to be John D was basically the prototype for Merlin and he was like this brilliant
Astrologer he actually did it a chart for Queen Elizabeth and for Mary Queen of Scots
I mean he didn't do it for Mary Queen of Scots
but he did a chart of her astrology one of the first people to do charts and stuff and
He said that she would be basically, you know killed and
Elizabeth would come into power so Mary Queen of Scots imprisoned him in the Tower of London
And then she died and then Elizabeth came into power Elizabeth took him as her court
Magician basically he spoke to angels. He came up with the Anokian system if you heard of it in like an Enoch
You know, yeah, yeah, yeah, so Enochian is a language from the angels
I'll show you what it looks like the Anokian alphabet. He actually
He couldn't really he was more of like a transcriber like he was very he couldn't channel
But he there's an obsidian mirror he had that came from South America a black shard of obsidian and he he met a guy
named
John Edward his name is Edward Kelly and Edward Kelly would see angels on them
And then D would write down everything that they would say and they've gotten very very detailed with it like I mean
amazingly mathematical and it's crazy, but eventually the angels told them to swap wives for a night and
They would get
the answers are looking for whatever they did that and then the angels stopped talking to them
and everything i'm gonna say that these are more like the money behavior if you ask me right well
the angels are very they were very oh oh was it a testament angel and they failed right there's
actually there's an angel named madimi madimi is an angel of mars and she was a very beautiful young
maiden but then she would also go into these wrathful wrathful appearances too and she was one
See it is very interesting. It is
And it is very I'm kind of like a barbarous kind of you know, very guttural like
Yeah, it's a very interesting look and it's like but they I mean it's very very detailed if you ever look into a no
Kean magic and things like that. I mean he
He had the largest library in England and everything and he you know, he eventually
You know, I eventually his house was is you know, the when he went to Austria or something like that
See a royalty his house was raided and stuff like that and
Pretty interesting. Okay. Here's Apollo one second. You look into John D. Look John D. He's fascinating
I'll show you his picture too because he is like the archetypal
Magician like a Merlin
Here's a picture John D. Oh, I
English mathematician and astronomer the really old like 16th century. Yes
He was for Queen Elizabeth. And so here's the most famous picture is
Right there
Yeah, same guy
Yeah, okay, that's Gandhi and and then Edward Edward Kelly was a kind of like a you know
He came to him answered like an ad or something like oh, I can like you know talk to
Spirit or whatever, but he was like he had both of his he had the tops of his ears chopped off because he was a thief
And so he would wear a hat always and he was kind of like a kind of like maybe
More of a nefarious reputation and everything but
He he would they would they would sit and then John you would write down everything that he would say and they have these
Diaries hundreds of pages long of these angelic transcripts. You would find it very interesting if you they're all for free online
You can yeah, but apparently yeah, apparently this John D was very prolific mathematician. Yeah
very brilliant, very, very, very, very brilliant. Um, and also magician, like magician, too. Like, um,
if you look into his math, yeah, it says, like, you can put math towards any situation, can't you?
Like, you can put maths towards any situation and sum it up.
Math, yeah, because I thought the daddy said that math, maths can explain it. A lot of things, what?
See, look at this.
you can see a picture of him here with a compass on the earth
and he was like he was looking he would like do politics and stuff
but the thing with him is like he was also looking for treasure
because a lot of the a lot of the people were like oh they were using magic to
like find treasure and things like that and the angels were like trying to like
trying to say they're not agreed right
Right and the angels what they said would lie to him in things like that
You know you can see and but there's interesting
There's also a picture of yeah, here's here's a picture of him with the angel. Um
This might be a
Yeah, this picture of
This and he's there's Edward Kelly right there with the hat on so you can't see his ears, right?
And then there's John D and there
they would see these angels and stuff on the plate.
That looks familiar, that picture.
Yeah, I mean, look into it, like really look into it,
because it's very, very interesting.
I found a path, and yeah, he came up with this thing
called the Steal of Truth.
And so this is like a geometric kind of thing right there.
It's very...
Crazy
And they have all these names of God all over it like all these names of God you can see that there's that there's a group
Chosen one
D was he was one of the main architects of the concept of the British Empire. Yes, exactly real vision
And he was a looks like he was a let me see looks like he was a cancer
And he died he was 81 years died in Mortlake. He had a house in Mortlake. What is he famous?
Oh, he was also he also had it. He's also signed things with 007. He had a 007 signature, which I can find
And then so he was the original double
I'll show you how he's how he signed it on his things John D. 007 it should look let me see
John D. Okay, but John D
Yeah, he would sign stuff with this
Oh
Yeah, it does have an alien link to it. Well, yeah, the nooky angels are very alien like too
Did it actually mean though the digits 0 0 7 or did it have this?
different it was a signature it says it says
007 was the badge number that was used for private messages between Queen Elizabeth's court and John D
So he was signed up on the
He was a spy a spy as well for the Queen, right?
Yeah, he's moving says he signed his letters with two circles symbolizing the two eyes indicating that he was the secret eyes of the Queen
Very interesting and I mean if you can look into like the
these these are Anokian
Alphabet study would do an Okian
Chart because they're just like so amazingly detailed
like yeah
He'd make these tables and they would go one by one
It's a part of the green screen is on but these are all like they would have these numbers and every single one of them
And they it's all mathematical. It's yeah, it's really really mean it's like
more complicated than I even I mean it's the lifetime of study but yeah the
Anokian holy tablet of it's also a form it is a form of magic that's still
practiced today you can there's something called the angelic calls you say
them in the Anokian language and they supposedly are very powerful and they
conjuring up these angels yeah and there if you translate them
They read very apocalyptic. I'll read one of the calls. Let me see Inokian call
One because there's I think they're they go into the ethers like Alistair Crowley did it. So
The first Anokian call it I'll pronounce it in
And how it was said and then I'll read it and what it means. Okay. It goes. Oh well
so new F
vorah sagae
Goho Iyade Ba El Ta Lo En Sa Ho Ka El Zod Vo En Pe Ho So He Ra Zo Do El Ro Ra Yi Ta Na Zod Pe Tza De Ge Ra Ah Ta Ma A Pe Ra Ge De Hes
hoel koa koa no ta hoa zod iem zod o de koem maho ta nobloholo zod ien so ba tahiel.
And it says, I reign over you, saith the God of Justice, in power exalted over the firmaments of
is as a through thrusting fire which measures your garments in the midst of my vestures and
trust you together as the palms of my hands whose seats I garnished with the fire of gathering
and which beautified your garments with admiration to whom I made a law to govern the holy ones
and which delivered you a rod with the ark of knowledge. Moreover, you lifted up your voices
whose beginning is not nor end cannot be, which shineth in the midst of your palace and amongst
you as the balance of righteousness and truth. Move therefore and show yourselves. Open the
mysteries of your creation. Be friendly unto me, for I am the servant of the same, your God,
the true worshiper of the highest." That's the first invocation, but there's like 33 or something
like that. It's pretty interesting. So is something supposed to happen now? Do the heavens part or
Yeah, there is a few if you do it in in earnest you do feel a very powerful energy here Chris K
What's up? What up? What up? What up? What up? What up? What up? What up? Hello?
No, I'm on my phone bro like what are you guys talking about dude there's some buster shit
What is your file?
No, I don't know I found that shit. What do you think about it?
I'm all fucking I'm drinking like I'm trying to be cool dude because I don't want to get like carried away
But I'm a celebrating bro. I want to parlay NFL parlay eight leg dude this Sunday like yesterday, whatever
I bet fucking seven bucks dude to win fucking 150 Doug and I hit that shit dude
I hit fucking I had what a what a parlay is if you bet on each team like
To win like I said, I was gonna put it in your discord if you want to see the ticket
Like I bet on eight. I bet on eight teams
I predict you know predicted eight teams of win and like if one team loses or whatever dude like you don't fucking uh, you lose
So I mean $7 to win 150 bucks bro. Shoot it all day. No, I mean
What
Music his name is music music is Marty he died
Yes, I know the guy. Yeah. Yeah, you know, Jamie Rose
Like both those guys are familiar with everybody. Yeah, so
And he was
he found me and
But but he would ask me sports betting
Yeah, I mean that's all I do dude. That's all I do sports bets, bro
Cuz I follow the NFL and I fucking I bet on Saturday night and fucking
Yeah, like a dude the Broncos man. I was a stressful bro, you know only I had $7 on it, dude
But I you know to win 150 bucks
Like fucking they were down they had 30 something points in the fourth quarter dude type shit, bro, and I was like
They came they came back to win dude by one point. I was like I went to the fucking the sportsbook, dude
I walked in I bet it a Westgate
Because it's like right by my house the Westgate sportsbook. I walked in I was like I have my ticket right in my hand
I was like a fucking walking to anybody when I was like flapping it around
You know I mean and it was like no no I was like flapping around. I fuck I said there's all these people still watching because uh
Sunday Sunday night football was still on dude if I went like rise I won
I was like I can't believe I eight leg eight legs means you fucking eight eight teams
I fucking bet on to win and they all they all want it's like an eight-way eight like parlay is pretty
It's like damn bro. I was like man at least I got seven because I started I stopped watching then my brother
He's like bro. They're fucking they just did it. They just get up
Coming back. I'm like, oh fuck shoot it. You know me. So yeah, I like sports
You like sports betting
So sports betting or like blackjack, but I only play blackjack downtown like Fremont area like Golden Gate
El Cortez cuz like I get crazy, bro
Like I fucking listen if the fucking if the dealer gets happy when which he fucking gets his 21 and it takes my chips away
I'm like, what are you happy about it? I talk mad shit to the dealer duck, you know, I mean and I can't do that on the strip because he
Well, we know your temper we've seen the fighting videos
Yeah, like fucking
Yeah, I'm surprised. I haven't got kicked out. But you know, I mean if I got my money on the table
I'm like, hey, you know fuck if I what are you talking about? They give me my cards
I'm like, hey, where's the waitress? You know, I mean and everybody at the table is like patting me on the back
They love me when I'm there, dude. I'm like, I'm like, who is this dude like fucking?
I can't even understand what you're saying. She's like calm down, sir. I am calm
Can I get a drink real quick? Where's the fucking the cocktail waitress? You know what I mean? Yeah, so
And like I don't care
From your fucking from your shit dude like you you want me to play you want me to give you my money or not
You know I mean like fucking
Listen, she's I'm like fucking securities like a certain dude calm down like I ain't I'm calm bro
Can we play it? Can we play some fucking blackjack or what dude? Like can I get a drink over here?
Like where's the cock? You know I mean
They're like, yeah, you know, they stay calm in those in those the very uh, I get pissed off
If the fucking dealer is happy that she beat me. I'm gonna talk shit. I'm like, does that make you happy, bro?
Like fun bonuses or something if they win a lot or do I mean do they get any incentives?
I don't know man. I have to fight like there's there's a I don't I
I mean, you know, it's not it's not every time I play blackjack did I get like that?
But I have to find like a good dealer like the last time I got crazy like that was some Korean chick
And she could like she's like, oh, no, no, no, no, like fucking she's fat and all this shit
I was like, fuck you, you know, fuck you dude
I need to find a dealer that I that kid like it's white and speaks English
Gras
Um, you know, I think
Koreans are pretty good at math not to be stereotypical, but I'll say they're pretty they can be I think that wasn't there a big ring of like these
Uh blackjack
Basically, they could count cards and they would go around and they got banned from all the casinos eventually because they got caught
Like yeah, there was something about it
Yeah, and I think they're a lot of them are Asian, you know
but yeah you're looking for the white the white person the white person's not
gonna be well somebody somebody that fucking speaks English that's like you
know that has a like you know a non-accent or whatever dude like you
know I mean but I think that was the only table open that night that I went
there that time I don't play blackjack that much like I said bro
Well, are you
Los Angeles with the hundred thousand dollars? I'm saying with me. I mean, it's looking like 90 it look at like 90
That's fine. That's fine. 90,000 is just perfect. I'm just kidding. That's I fucking um
Man, I wish I was that parlayer one bro. I wish I would have fucking put more money on it
You know, I mean like it would have been like so much bigger like I you know, but who's the who's the fucking say
Let me a go to your discord here. I'll put it on there right now
Well, you can bet you can bet on everything, you know, you can bet on anything nowadays, right? It's like that's what keeps the
some people interested in like
Otherwise boring sports, you know, you can bet on anything
I'm not good at gambling. I actually I'm good at the sports betting I did with music biz Marty. He would send me like
Whenever he would win and it was just a few times he passed away shortly after I met him
But he was on my show and he would I said basically he asked if I could do tarot to predict
The outcome of sports games. I was like, I think that's a misuse of terror who I wouldn't like do that
But I was like just tell me the color of the team's pants
I'll have a look at how their butts look and if I like the team's name and I'll make a prediction based on that
Yeah, it's it's rough dude. I've tried I've tried to like I need to like uh, like predict
I need to fucking like a time machine or are seeing in the future, dude
And I've
Like I'm ready to cheat especially in a casino
right
Yes, I want I want to see if they fucking if the roulette ball lands on bread or black
Do you like fucking you know 10 10 maybe 15 seconds ahead of time and I'll be fun
I'll be a millionaire. I'm trying to always wins and gambling is like, you know, usually it's like a losing
But some people get looked at that way my brother was like I'm confident in a bunch of places, but he would
You know like go to casinos and he was really pretty successful, but you know it turns into an addiction and it can be kind of
Yeah, there were a
There was one time
Next one time I left the fucking I was on Fremont
El Cortez
Playing blackjack and I fuck I was like, you know, I had like I started off with like maybe Twitter bucks
I ended up losing or whatever, but I got drunk. I got like hella drinks for free or whatever
I mean, you know, I'm paying I'm playing playing blackjack and losing but you know, I mean when I left the table
I'm like, hey, I'm like, I'll be back. Listen, I'm gonna I'm gonna win so much money
You're goddamn gonna see it. I'm gonna make you bank or up to it and just like walked away
everybody was like, damn, that was crazy, you know what I mean?
And I just walked out.
You're crazy, but that's what makes you fun, you know?
Yeah.
I don't I don't you know, I haven't played blackjack recently
But I can't do it any of the big because I'm already trespass at all MGM properties Jesus really
Yeah, I got I got arrested fool like fucking the last Super Bowl dude. I was all drunk. Oh
Yeah, so I mean you got it like I have a list I gotta look at my phone like you know
I could they have facial recognition type shit. Yeah
But I listen I I've talked to them
Called them and like there's an email and they want me to like send like a an email to them
So like asked to be like on untressed pass, you know, I just haven't done it. I'm pretty sure they will let me it's been like two years
well, you know
That's like target if you shop to the target you can't go to any target ever again because they have the facial recognition
They'll come grab you right away. You know, it's like it's gonna get crazier, but uh
I know do you know scribbles? You know scribbles is Chris? Yeah, he came out here to Vegas multiple times
I have his I hit him on DMs on Instagram and he wanted I told him like let's like stream together and
It was me and whappy and he's like, oh man. I'm he's like scared of whappy. He's also
I think he's banned also. He he team he maced
some security guard on the strip so he's banned from the strip I think and
Well, yeah, probably depending on what hotel they ban you from their properties like, you know
Yeah, and I just did a reading for him in his his wife
And recently and I was on yeah, he's really cool. I like how's he looking? How's his reading looking? Oh
It's good. I think he screwed up
He's got he's got I mean he has sisters
Yeah, I think about as like I think as like his wife Kim comes up really really strong and I was like
I was like, she's a good woman. She came up with like emperors energy
I was like stick stick with her, you know and like, you know, you have to keep begging for forgiveness
You're gonna be on a
She also got she also got she's also Capricorn like I am and I was like and then the Capricorn the devil card came up
Which is like the devil and that particular card had like the devil with the marionette strings
I'm like, okay, that's him. That's him on the strings and you
You can go on oh here we have a YouTube stream yard who's this oh, it's Arthur Beck
What was going on there? Yo, it's chaotic today in the morning. I'm back here. What's going on? Good morning
I got in the morning big big energy guys. I have some big big big energy
Hey site go to your discord real quick and look go to the jet of the regular chat
I sent the the the
The ticket that the one I want on dude
Shut the fuck how much you win?
$7 and I won 150 bucks eight Lake Parley
to
The other day and psyche knows this you were just like oh like oh and we're done word
Asian pussy
Well, yeah, you know, I was like probably blackout drunk dude like I'm trying to chill weren't
You've done it numerous times on streams and I asked myself
I've asked people like yo is he is he sick like is he mentally challenged and they're like no
Yeah, this is how he acts. I just get carried away dude. I get like I'm like hyped up. I get hyped up
Why do you do that though? Like people are talking about something and then you're in the background. Oh chicken nuggets and word I
Don't know my bad, bro. My bad
W's there's all these W's on his parlay
You're really scary like and here's boys
He's oh my god
There's someone posted it ally magic computers
Video I can't show it because he always privacy, but yes, you know like all those teams on the side right there
Like they all won like I had if one team lost I wouldn't have won like all those teams won like you know
So it's like eight legs, bro. It means it means eight leg means like it's eight
eight bad you know eight bets in one ticket you know I mean hey that's pretty amazing $7.00 yeah one
Collected 146 70 pretty cool. Yeah, so what do you do that? Like you never said why you just said sorry?
I did that I don't know I don't I don't realize that I do it
I guess like if I if I like interrupt by like treading you say a threat
Yeah, you specifically see the n-word you're like and we're chicken nuggets and it's like what
Well, we know he does like to use that word
Yeah, you know, especially I don't want to say the n-word on psych because he's on he's on YouTube and I got respect
And I don't want to get him in trouble. So I'm gonna try my best not to say that, you know
We go on tatter bait together you can say that you have to call it you have to call it to me
You have to call me that are you getting are you monetized on YouTube, right? It's like, yeah, I am
That's that's I mean
I mean, how much I mean, you know, you know, you don't got to say it, you know
Well, I actually had a I'm having a very good month because it's it's goes to bro
I don't know if you know, it's goes so that you got ads on like all your shit
But you like half the shit have to fucking the the ads don't make very much
It's like the it's either the memberships plus super foundations and the donations. Yeah, that's the major
I know but it's crazy because like I mean, I don't know if it if you do this but like half the
Just like podcasts or whatever that you do you have to delete them a lot of times because people get crazy and you can't you know
I mean, right, but you know what now I figured out you can
edit them right you can edit them and
Now that I have a computer I'm able to do it easier and faster and so I'm able to
Edit stuff right yeah, YouTube like has a built-in thing where you can like clip like cut out parts of the
Vod the Vod. Yeah, really?
Yeah, so why does salmon always go to this specifically? I can't cross the four-hour mark line
I gotta end this because after four hours you can't you can't do the
Cut in I think it's like or I thought it was six hours, but you can that's what I'm saying
It's not it's not four hours or six hours. They've actually made it longer. Yeah
You can blur it and you can mute it and stuff like that still I think I don't even think you can use that option unless you are like, you know
Verified with YouTube or whatever dude. I don't know. I'm a partner. I'm a YouTube partner. I basically work for you
I work with I'm like I'm like a
Partner I'm YouTube partners what they call it. I mean, you know, I that's why I say I wish the best for you on YouTube
Man, it's it's gonna be it's hard didn't because like they're
Since April I've been a month. I think April so it's already
October so April May June is like us
What are your thoughts on beta lately is everything good?
Me? I went to her show tonight and, you know, she's like, kind of like, you know, I was on there and she was like, I came on with my vegan, I said I was vegan patriot and I ruined the blonde wig and she was like, and then blogger was there and this woman, Victoria K.
Yeah, there was crap.
Yeah, and like, and then she was, she was like, well, she's like, psyche didn't come up for me, came up for blogger and.
This woman I
Even talked to that woman it or and I don't like blogger very much
I came up to cheer her up and like to be
Maybe give her a like giggle, but I don't just kind of didn't take it that way
And so I'm kind of like would you like me would you meet her in real life or whatever? Sure
You know you know Alexander mayors. I met Alexander mayors after like a month of knowing Alexander
You met Vita. Yeah, and Alexander was for like a lot further away. And like
That's the that's the black chick, right?
Yeah, I read I read her tarot one time and I was pretty spot-on and she I think she uploaded a video of me doing it type shit. Yeah
Yeah, she's she's she's familiar with you. Yeah. Yeah, and
Alexander and I are on a 30-day
Break break or something that's kind of weird. I've never heard anybody become friends and tell the other one
We're on a 30-day break period. Okay, like
That's gotta be one of the weird shit fine because it's like it's like it gives everyone space like you know
Untangled entangle any energies because there's now there's there might be triangulation with the you know beta stuff
Because she's weird
I should come down dude meet up with you bro, and then we can go we go fucking meet up with with betas dude in Orange County
You know what I mean? I would I mean I would like to but be I think beta is not like I don't think she meets that many people
I don't think she's she'll meet she'll meet me dude. She's she already told me like fucking I was gonna go down there like
Few months ago or whatever she wanted me to like come down and shit like fucking and I should dude. Maybe she's like
Maybe it'd be good for me. Like maybe I can like, you know, I'm trying to hook up bro type shit, man
Yeah
Dude, listen, I listen I'm from fucking I'm from San Bernardino Doug. I'm from I'm from Southern California, dude, right?
So what is that? You know, I listen I would love I am in Vegas
I would love to move back there, but it's it's fucking you know, I don't I don't have any houses
I have no place to go like if I could like meet up with her dude and like chill with her like fuck
I mean just make sure you clear it would be the first don't
Yeah, well, yeah, of course, dude, you know, like fucking
What would you be like your four play? What would you do?
Would be I don't know. She's I feel like she's a freak in the sack. So I mean I fuck whatever she wants to do
Dude, I'm down, you know
So she probably likes a bomb in her pussy. Hey, I mean a bomb. What do you think about this woman?
What do you think about this woman right here?
It looks okay, I guess it's okay
Hold on. What do you think about this one right here? Wait, I you know, I don't want to get too specific here
But I mean psych what we could like if we meet up with beat us
Yeah
Well, how about this? I got I got this Chris. What do you think? I always get like vote like well
I don't want to get to a I don't know if I can trouble
I want I want psych to keep his his bods up his
Podcasts and I don't want to be the reason why he has to delete it for some crazy fit
So I'm gonna like just chill. You know, I mean, it's okay
You know, you know, please if it's about like, you know, but what do you think of vegan patriot? I'm you could tell the line
Don't don't be afraid to say something just don't say the end word
Chris chatterbait is calling our name
Chatterbait is doxing you guys. No, it's it's calling our name like come yeah, dream on me
Hold on you want to you want to see him naked? I
Do I want to see him naked. What the fuck?
What I'm a red-blooded homosexual man. This is me
I forgot you were gay dude
to
Well, no, like I'm not listen. I'm not gay, but I'm not a homophobe like I don't care or whatever but like fucking
If I if I was gonna maybe like fucking a gay out or whatever
I mean psych would be like I would think about it with him. You know, I mean, I mean
I don't have to say I don't have to say it's that's getting clipped
Why because he's he's available available because he's the only one that you know
Because I'm cute and gorgeous, right? No, I mean, I've known I've known I've known him through the internet or whatever like for like what?
a couple years
I give amazing head
I do, I do
I got what the fuck is going on bro
Hey, we're opening minds opening hearts. Hey, so so a Brandon K says Chris
What's Wappy's Addy if you I don't know if you can put in the back tat or something like that?
Abana, what's wrong with you crying, Abana?
I'm gonna be the one crying lovely ladies trying to that's gonna be my face when I'm like
They're all laughing their asses off. Oh, I'm in trouble school bathrooms is here
See me mad at me. Hold on boy. Hold on another question. Oh Brandon's here too. Hold on. There you go
Brandon yo, what's up, bro? Yo, and Athens are you there?
Why would I be mad at you? Of course not think you left me in the trenches taking grenades over there
Over there first man, I went over there to protect myself jack
Yeah, but I didn't understand what was going on. I thought that you didn't want to jump
Don't worry
They want you to jump over there all three of us was no no
I I said right from the beginning that no no, I'm not involved in this man
I just went over there just tell him that hey, it's not me trying to jump on panel. That's all gotcha
But I was just joking anyways about yeah, yeah, I know
But I didn't know what the fuck was going on
Well either did blogger he seemed to be very frustrated, but
No one's watching vlogger that guy's a weirdo. Yo, he was out of it. He was out of it
Warm it up, Chris
I was I was taking a piss dude, I didn't want to be off like pee and all out on the on the fucking mic, you know
the
No, they're mad at me because I exposed gamble, bro
I made him quit streaming and now he has to see a psychiatrist
It is on psych meds and all fucked up in the head
Well, I mean, that's sounds like his personal problem
Oh
Hey, bro, I don't expose a is a your pedophile, bro. Oh, yeah
You know, I'm pretty much Alexandra. Are you friends of Alexandra? Alexandra knows, you know
Discuss all about yeah Alex dude. She got mad at me, but we're still friends
I think same. I think we're cool. We're just on a little break, but I actually got to meet her and stuff.
Hold on, Brandon K, do you know who KK is?
Hello?
KK?
KK, yeah, I know.
Wait, are you that weirdo that they start exposing you?
What are they exposed Faggot what are they exposed a whoa whoa language?
What are they exposed to the question? He just said he just asked you a question. He didn't
Know I suppose that truth was to you want to see a picture want to see what she looks like
No, cuz it's
Hold on hold on this guy should not be on here. I know I've told you this many times, but
If you type his name on YouTube, you're going to see him speaking to minors on the internet, bro.
Why is he here? This is that weirdo, bro. Get him out of here.
I have no idea about any of it, so I can't.
It's on YouTube. Type it in. Type his name. Just type it in.
I don't have to give you research right now.
Oh, my God. You don't have time to research a weirdo?
Hey, look. Come on, dude.
That's... This is Alexander and I, and we went to... We've met recently. I'll show you this here.
Oh, my God. This is weird, bro. Your luck. I can't leave the call right now because I'm a driver.
They just go Alexander. Yeah, you see porn hold up. I'm the weirdo, but everybody's there, right?
That motherfucker bro have him on video with some girl and the girls. Oh, we met in high school and so shut up shut up
They're both in high school. No, you're lucky. I can't leave the phone. This is so weird
You're talking shit, bro, so I could get you broke
Who's running their mouth right now to me, bro?
Shut your fucking face
Who's running their mouth to me right now, bro? Jacob. What are you gonna do Jacob? What don't worry about that?
Yeah, exactly this hour, bro. Q army owns you dude. This is Q army, bro. They're weird. Brad is Brad and Q, right? Yeah
The person like the hold on well, no, I'm on my phone. I could barely see the names and shit, bro
I'm all drunk, you know
Hey Chris, Cap is running his mouth to you like threatening to kill you and all kinds of shit.
Were you talking about WAP?
Yeah, just recently, wasn't that recently?
Yeah, uh, and it's crazy that I haven't really like talked to him that much since that happened.
And you know what, uh, I fucking, it's, it's like, dude, I didn't do nothing wrong, dude.
Like I'm just, I've, you know, you guys want to tell, tell, hear the story?
Yeah
KK has
I'm a weirdo at least I don't abuse children bro. Do I go and grab make these accusations? Okay, you talk to
Right there
I'm sure someone will fill me in on it, but I
Did a monkey ab stream bro, okay
And what they did is when I would skip somebody they would just take a screen
No, I didn't
This guy's aware as soon as I park. I'm leaving bro school of assets. If you type in his name, you're gonna see everything, bro
That's what I'm saying. He has a laptop now, so he has the accessibility to type it on.
I'm trying to host the show right now. I can't be like researching it.
He can do all this AI shit, but he can't type in it.
He's filling you in.
Exactly. This is so weird. I'm probably trying to...
I feel like all these people make this accusation that he's a PDF, he's a PDF,
anyone is a PDF on this planet. What's going on?
the
By a very long time
That's not you like him he sounds very serious bro, that's Arthur's bro that dude literally glazes Zaya Zaya
That was Arthur that you glazed Zaya was 20 30 years old with a 16 year old shut your bitch
The fact that he just left like that
you just got stupid
Can we stop talking about
Everybody's been accused everything
Hey, who's that guy is there who's that guy talking is he there is like an indian guy is he indian brandon
no not Brandon like there's somebody here that's German and Greek
well no like there's uh you guys you guys haven't like uh
i mean if you haven't checked it out dude go and look up um indian christmas music
on youtube and uh they see like a like in like in
the
It's like a super funny, but yeah, I don't think well, I think it's probably I
Don't know if they sing in English and stuff. I love Hindu music. I even didn't yeah
pronunciation
They use like a sitar
Oh, I love the sitar sitar. I mean, yeah, it's like you could play real quick, bro
Like the first the first verse dude, and I
Don't want to I'll listen to it
No, I actually one of my friends out here in Vegas is like
Well, he's his parents are from India and they moved to Canada then he moved from Canada to like Vegas
And he's my concert buddy. We don't see punk like punk rock shows and like metal. He's my he's an Indian guy
You can look at my Instagram
Suicidal tendencies you are suicidal tendencies with him and shit. I don't know
I hear some stories thing that is about this Chris K guys, you know, you like to beat up
Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris
No, I'm reformed bro. I'm reformed. I I regret a lot of stuff. I've streamed in the past
The first time I met you I was on psyches channel and you gave me a reading
You were the first person to do it and you were just like this laid-back
Relax guy and then like a week later. I came on and you came on it was like like oh, yeah
He's a relaxed guy and they're like
Chris, I'm like, yeah, I met him last week, and then you went fucking insane, I know I get carried away sometimes, bro.
Oh, he's someone's a bad person sometimes people
That's why he laughed at it. You know, it's fucking crazy. I was laughing though. It's fucking nuts. Hey, man. How are you?
That was funny
You made me laugh
Hey, get off my nuts. Yeah, it is okay. Let me play my game
Oh my god, hey, who's that? Oh, okay. Let the Apollo live his life
No, you guys might hear the wappy wappy flanker story real quick. I want to hear that Indian fucking song
Indian Christmas music here right now. I'm not in the Christmas beer. I just don't know if it's copyright. I mean
Be a little bit cautious cuz I'm all you know, I'm playing I'm gonna play it on my stream next time I stream
I'm not you know, I'm on my phone right now
All like I'll listen to it, but I love but I do love you know, Hindu
Music, I listen to a lot of it like chanting and things like that. I think Sanskrit is a
gorgeous language
Lot of religions. Yeah, Hinduism. I mean, yeah, it's very it's very interesting
Brandon is back. Okay, hold on a second
I miss I miss seeing bad religion again, dude. They were out here in Vegas for I
When we're a young festival, dude, but it was like $400 for tickets and then you know, I saw him I saw him in 97 and
They were fucking they rocked the fucking house and then I saw him again in 06 they opened for Pearl Jam and
Actually, no was earlier than that. It was 03 Pearl Jam closed the spectrum in Philadelphia with four shows
Before they knocked it down and bad religion opened for them the first two nights and social D opened for them the second two nights
And, uh, he came out, yeah, he came out and sang 21st century digital boy with Ben religion,
Eddie Vedder. It was really cool. It was really cool.
That's so fucking dope, dude. Yeah, I mean,
Great, I know what it is. They're like, they're like, you know, I love the band. I think Greg Graffin is the lead singer's name and
I mean, he's been out in Vegas a lot. He did a book signing. He has a book. He wrote a book. I mean, he was in the books
Yeah, I'm a tax, you know, that's like people don't realize that you know the fucking
The label epitaph the record. Yeah. Yeah
It's it's the biggest label in the fucking 90s like nobody can say no, right?
Like, you know, in that scope that you saw that shit though, dude. You say saw it in Philly. I
Saw them first in 97 on Randall's Island
So that means they're there with their album that was not trying to think what album was out in 97 dude like, you know
Mmm, that's a good question. I can't remember but you know at that time
That's when you know right before blink 182 hit and it was just major like like pop punk became so big
So believe it or not, it's
Blink 182 was like there is he's playing it. They're playing somebody's playing it. Wait, hold on. Okay
I like it
Wait start it over start it over cuz the first part's the best, you know
I
Just got a body back come on
It is what it is, you know what I'm saying, I can't change it.
I can't change it. It is what it is.
Yeah.
They sound joyous, I mean, that's what Christmas is supposed to be like a joyous I know I try not to laugh
But because they're getting into it, you know, and it's just their accent is just like funny, right?
I think it's in goods good good spirits
We think their accent is funny and it is but like
Well, hey psych listen psych here's the thing look at that video look how many views bro millions, you know, I mean he's doing something, right?
right
Apollo, yeah
There's like Midwest accents or can be fun. I mean, it's like that's because there's 250 million people in the country is so fucking large
But Apollo no, I don't touch him. It is what it is. You know, it's not
He's Chris is right. It is funny, but Apollo just a quick question. Do we sound funny when we try to speak German?
What is our accent sound like when we try to speak German?
Wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein Auto, wir waren ein
I got I got the New York. I got the New York New York accent on point
We would you say my accent yeah, we sound horrible though. We can't speak. No, I mean I can do I can do a New York accent
I don't know
But for me, you saw it sound funny, you know, your accident was funny.
Listen to the way I say, of course, you hear me?
Of course, you know what I mean?
No, I got what you want to get some.
Listen, you want to get some Yankee tickets?
I got me. I got to go downtown Brooklyn.
I got me my cousin Bobby down.
Be honest, bro, I'm from New York.
You got too much.
You got too much Boston in that.
But there's a little too much pronunciation, man.
It's a little bit of what the fuck you mean is he fucking dead dad's good. He's like I got dead. It's like I let all fucking baby guy
No, you listen you guys want to get some good some good tickets
I got to go down me my cousin Bobby downtown Brooklyn, you know and like the last time I went down there
They had the streak rocked off and I'm trying to get a bagel. I'm like, can I get a bagel?
No, no R in there. There's no R, we went down there, we went down there.
I think it's pretty saw. I mean, it's a pretty good New York accent.
It's hard to do, bro. You know, you remember the Sopranos?
Alright singer, you know to check that played metal
So she wanted to be an actress and she went to fucking acting classes to get rid of her accent because she had such a trouble like
You know not getting out of that Brooklyn accent and then the first fucking role she gets after all that work is the soprano
Yeah, because it's so
Yeah, the Brooklyn accent. Oh, okay. So like water coffee, but it's New York. It's all the metropolitan area, New Jersey
Okay, okay
Okay, so I got a down cuz my cousin Bobby. He lives downtown. He got me
You know me we'll get but straw me and fuck it. Hope it's open
But we got me we gotta meet downtown my cousin Bobby and here God. He's got the ticket
We're gonna get you got the Yankees you want to see the Yankees come with me. We'll go downtown Brooklyn
some water some coffee on the way some waters and coffee you can be in as a
pro every time mana calls them on the east coast like you know the states the
first thing is always have you met Bill Clinton are you from Arkansas oh yeah
I want to see I want to go to see the Yankees play if you want to get some
tickets I gotta meet up with my cousin Bobby downtown
I got to meet my cousin
You know I mean
You buy two I'll give you one on the arm by to you got a how I mean I'll be saying
Hey, do you want to come up? Are you finished your painting yet?
I like I like that New York accent dude, you know, I was thinking about moving to New York, man
But it's like cold in the winter, you know
Chris move with me. I'll keep you warm. Okay. Yeah, right near the beach
You go up a west side of Manhattan is double that
Yeah, and Brooklyn really cheap. So a lot of people used to go to Brooklyn
You know to get the cheaper rent and then work in the city because when we say the city we mean Manhattan
But now Brooklyn is the same fucking fucking dead. What the fucking means he fucking he laid out on the street like a fucking baby
Come on
here let me say real quick
I love some of some of my favorite rap music is fucking from east coast do like Wu Tang method man
Yeah, that shit is fucking hard as fuck. You're just doing this. Yeah. Yeah, you can't buy in new yorker
I just heard you doing the Wu Tang skit. You god. That's what you got. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, uh, I'll put the 36 chambers. It's the ghost
That shit is that shit is like that shit is so good. Like I'll bump that shit like today
Was it fucking a cash moves everything around me cream get the money dollar dollar bill y'all
Yeah, tell us about the wappy story, so I want to hear that bro sing it Apollo. All right wappy time
Like a fucking what the fuck
He laid out like a fucking baby
That's method man saying that shit. Yo, I want to hear Apollo sing
That shit's hard, bro, I love that shit, bro
And I don't eat green eggs with Sam
Yeah, yeah, hell yeah method man is is fucking
Yeah, I mean that's like my top five I had stuff I was like a top five big like most like rappers method is like like three
You know I mean, I like that's I like I like I'm from Cali dude type shit bro
I'm from West Coast you but that shit that's that method man fucking
One of my favorites is the the least known one the the eighth member fucking master killer
Because he was only on one verse in that first album, but the second double album. He was on a lot more
The mass yeah, what is it fucking uh album as a man fucking uh
Met the man met the man's got to cow to cow to cow TCAL to cow
Oh my gosh, everyone's doing well. I'm getting an accent overlook the cow. Oh
My gosh, but it's great. I have a California accent. I have a little bit of a
New York accent so I we didn't hear yours your Brooklyn accent
I mean, I like little Kim, but that's not really like she I guess she is from Brooklyn
Reptiles trying to throw a couple crooked smiles take your kindness for weakness. They foul New York
Beloved how the guns help pow another on the broad pull the double-cross. I can't I'm tired. There's there's the inwards in that
Himmy not Tom pissy drunk up the himmy and ready
So that's the album. It's a it's a fuck. What album is it?
Isn't he did he from the East coast? Yeah, I think there's your mouth there. They're all from New York
That that's the hip-hop New York York
You know, it's crazy dude. I would be down. I'll be down to go do a diddy party, dude, you know
Yeah, I'll be all up or whatever whatever bro, they probably there's probably like all kinds of drugs alcohol. I'm let's go
No, what's fucked up man, did he fucking these bitches fucking went they did the shit like fucking a voluntarily dude
And now later on they're gonna fucking cry about it type shit, bro. That's why he's locked up, dude
You know, I mean
Situations take photographs and then like they had
No, I say let him out. I say Trump pardon him, bro. Let did he out, bro
Pages here, pages here. Hold on one second.
Page, page, page. Page is going to drop some words in the house, yeah?
Okay, let's hear your New York accent.
It's drop some whizzy on the hisie. Come on. Try and go down here. You want listen a page
You want to get some good Yankee tickets? I let me get a hold of my cousin Bobby. I gotta meet him downtown Brooklyn
We'll get some good
Yankees get the fuck out of here
Excellent
I don't know what I'm talking about, but I'm not sure what I'm talking about, but I'm not sure what I'm talking about, but I'm not sure what I'm talking about, but I'm not sure what I'm talking about, but I'm not sure what I'm talking about, but I'm not sure what I'm talking about, but I'm not sure what I'm talking about, but I'm not sure what I'm talking about, but I'm not sure what I'm talking about, but I'm not sure what I'm talking about, but I'm not sure what I'm talking about, but I'm not sure what I'm talking about, but I'm not sure what I'm talking about, but I'm not sure what I'm talking about, but I'm not sure what I'm talking about, but I'm not sure what I'm talking about, but I'm not sure what I'm talking about, but I'm not sure what I'm talking about, but I'm not sure what I'm talking about, but I'm not
Last time I took a cat attack. I took I think a cat a taxicab downtown and I
Don't think I can I was in the army with some guys from Boston who called the water fountain a bubbler
Yeah
What's your what's your highest rank you got? I
Got out. I was an E4
So you went through boot camp and you liked you that you just left cuz you wanted to
I was medically discharged, ah, come on buster. What'd you do? I'm not gonna tell you what I did
Man, well listen, would you join me there be a secret secret top level?
You know, that's cool
You know, I got the doughnuts. I did whatever I was fucking told to do
Yeah, I regret I regret bro
I wish I would have joined back when I was fucking when my stepdad
Suggested I would do it when I was like 19 my stepdad was a
That's what the US Army needs. I'm a racist. Yeah, right. I'm no
No, I wish I would have joined I wish I would have joined bro back in the day, dude and
I never did all I wanted to do a skateboard smoke weed do meth and that's all I that's all I wanted to do
Hey, well, that's what it was bro. I used to sell meth and shit, bro
I wish I wouldn't have done it dude, you know, that's why I have fell my goodness
In your country and I was selling
No, I regret I regret it, bro
Like fucking I have some felons that don't go away. I have a strike in California on my record, dude
It sucks dude. I can't love a lot of jobs. I can't get I can't fucking do I can't fucking work
I can't deal cards or do anything with money
Yeah, I think I've seen you up here before Chris K one night you were talking about it
Yeah
Wait, I thought wait. This is a wait a minute. This is a hold on because I'm on my phone, bro
Amanda
Well, there wasn't your name that about that old-school movie with the car
No
Okay, somebody else then
Christine Christine. Yeah. Yeah, I read her cards
Don't call this which name
She might summon her and no no Christina's not a big fan anymore. She's actually she's actually
She's attacking ghost lately
Even summer because she was like saying like you know and there's such a summer
You know some of her very good friends, but she's telling summer. Oh, you know like ghost should be donating
Right summer instead. I mean it's like yes, and I really do support summer and I you know I am
I think she does is a deserving a very deserving to get donations, but it's like people can decide who they want to donate
For what purpose?
Yeah, so
So many pennants get donations, okay? Why does she care who?
Abitablet donating to what is your problem and then she go to beta and say hey
Take care of our beta and convince him to don't donate to
Who the fuck are you?
Yeah, I give my money to who I want to I dare somebody to tell me who to fucking donate
Right. Well, I think Christine Christine's mad because I think last night
her crystal Marie came on and said that Christine was donating to this guy blade and like maybe
Encouraging him. Yeah, I thought was that was nuts
I have to before I forget though, I have to say this and I've said this to school before
There was a Jewish family
Here where I grew up at and they were originally from New York
No offense, but school sounds just like the lady his voice
And and I don't mean
It's just that whole oh, yeah, honey, you know just I don't know how
I don't even describe it that whole.
It's okay.
I mean, it sounds like kind of like Bill Clinton
a little bit.
Yeah, well, yeah.
I mean, I did grow up in South Arkansas.
But, you know, God bless their soul.
They were very nice Jewish people and anyway.
I always had very close, like just growing up.
There's a lot of close Jewish friends like nothing. Oh, I have a lot of Jewish donators
I mean, it's a few and far between here Jewish ex-girlfriends. I mean one of my doctors is Jewish
But he's not originally from here. He's originally from nose man. I don't know if it's for Jewish people
Is it Martha Stewart is you I think she was Martha could stylish his pole
He calls me his favorite Gentile and I call him my favorite Jewish man. Oh
I work pretty closely with the Jewish family for a long time, so I get to know a lot of their stuff.
Do as many as you speak with a long nose, right? With a long nose?
Uh...
Bloggers?
Well, I mean, I'm half Italian and I have a big nose, so I don't go based on noses.
I was a guy... I had a nose job, my nose was so big.
Like, I had like, it kind of looked like a nose job.
Really?
Yeah.
you can see my you can see how like
oh yeah it's perfect
oh my jesus christ
it was hooked
indian native american or something like that
hey blogger
but yeah i did have a nose job because
it was like a little bit too big for my
frame but um
It was just like it just was kind of like
When they give people nose jobs, dude, they put them to sleep, bro, they get like a
You ought to see what they do when they do a knee replacement mom was filled
That was funny to see a doctor straddle your leg, okay?
It's been an age like a old grape or potato, you know what I mean?
I'm just gonna let it happen.
Ray, you're fine.
Actually, my dad had DNA test, too.
My dad had, I guess, Ashkenazi on his.
Oh, really?
It didn't show up in mine.
I think Alana had like 3% juice or 4%.
I'd have to find the paperwork.
Yeah, I mean I and I go I mean I've got you know Italian and I mean I believe a lot of European though
I look like my Italian grandfather
Someone have a hose
No, it's perfect though. It's a perfect tip. They I mean they school. I didn't have this tip before they sculptured it
Yeah, they did a good job. Yeah, it was the guy that did James Bond's facelift. He was doing was doctor
Does Rhino mean nose in Greek?
Yes, I think so.
To that cost, dude.
I figure that out.
Rhino plasticis are like, you know, I think a few thousand dollars.
They're a few thousand dollars.
They're not.
No, it doesn't.
You know, I want to say my dad just had most.
So we went into his nose and got a new nose.
Because rhino rhinoceros egg, you know the big horn and then rhino plasty
That it was like ancient Greek
No, it's Greek
I don't think so.
I didn't have a bar mitzvah.
Yeah, you're right. I get to go see my favorite Greek this week Apollo
Now his name is Dr. G
with with a big eyebrows. Yes, I'll be giving you share eyebrows. I tell him I want to take him
and get his eyebrows waxed and he just takes his head and says, Oh, no, these old guys don't do this.
Give him lots of uzo so he passes out and then pluck him when he's asleep. Yeah
Uzo is good. It's very good. It's like a but he's even though he has a crappy eyebrows. He's still a good-looking man
I'm giving that though
Apollo Apollo, what are your questions, huh? Is it Middle Eastern questions? What is it?
Yeah, I don't know if it's the right time. I don't want to interrupt the flow, you know, but I have a question, I have a question, listen, I saw that, okay, I don't want to go too political, I saw the Trump, I load the Qatar.
Kata Country, you know the Kata King?
Yes, I'm aware.
Abish in Idaho?
Yes.
What the king was in Idaho
We send we send a lot of our our pilots in that to to the US to be trained
That's two totally different things, but it's a good question. Okay. So to answer your question,
we have other joint bases. Okay. We have other joint bases. Like I believe for some reason,
I don't know why I'm thinking this. We have like Singapore or some other country.
I don't think it was doing that.
We have multiple joint.
Right, right.
It's not even a joint base.
They're just trained.
And illegal bases, too.
I think about Cuba.
I mean, that's fucking crazy.
OK, can we let Amanda talk, please?
Just let me.
They're right on the money.
Essentially, they're like winting space in a way.
We're essentially aiding them, I believe,
in training pilots, from what I understand.
What I have an issue with is that's where we keep the nukes, okay?
And that's a real reason they do you got nukes all over the place.
We do have nukes all over the place, but we have a large presence there. So, um,
and all of this is stored in a Kirtland Air Force base here. I'll shut up and let you finish.
No, Amanda, but you just hit it the nail on the head. It's we do it
Renting space for nuclear presence to have a nuclear presence, you know, basically towards Russia. Would you like to not agree?
Well, this all started in my opinion school. It goes back to that with the kingdom
And if you go back remember, they gifted him an airplane. Okay, let's go back. Yes, what which I think is a huge problem
I think it's a personal opinion
It's not a gift
So it's kind of like, you know, everybody's all up in arms about Oh Hamas in Israel. It's a it's a peace deal
No, it's not no telling how much we paid Hamas for that deal. Okay?
I would love to know how many billions of dollars we paid them this morning. Oh, yeah
The base in your chair, it's only for they don't have access to
Something else, right? They shouldn't know. No, we would never give them
Okay. Okay. I don't think about this. So I'm just talking about a nuclear
presence. So we have nukes all over the place that we have them all over the
second, think about in the 60s, the second that Russia got close to us with
Cuba. You see what fucking happened? Like that's why he's like, but yes,
because we listen to to be fair.
America wasn't going around the world threatening to be taken over countries, whereas the Soviet Union was.
Bro, we didn't threaten you.
That's a good point.
Listen, I don't...
You live in a fucking...
I'm sorry, bro, to just cut you off.
But, like, look at McKinley. Do you know why he was assassin?
Nated we took over Hawaii that was him. We have a base on Cuba because of him Puerto Rico Guam
Philippines I could go on and on American Samoa
You're right. We just take it over though. We're worse. All right. Well, well, I want to say this much and guys
I have been playing this since the very beginning and I know I'm a woman
But some of you know what I did in the military
China is our number one existential threat. I sent you a thing from 60 Minutes Apollo.
I don't know if you've had a chance to watch it. They are literally breaking into local
water sources now and guys. China is the Visigoths as we ought to run.
Yes, absolutely. That's what's going to happen. But you want to know something about what you're trying to do.
I wasn't trying to knock you about you know, we're worse than Russia every empire in the history of time
Does the same thing that we've done?
You have to have a presence you have
To the world that's that's the point the Soviet Union is clearly the bigger threat
Who do you think took down Facebook and everything yesterday guys?
It's hard to say that though, bro.
When you see the biggest threat, like who dropped it, bro.
Think about it.
God, I'm dying.
Come back, you know.
I get it, but it was the earliest that we're making all the threats,
doing all the stuff.
I mean, like I said, we're putting them so close.
to America, bro. I'm sorry. Listen, I understand they had
I do understand that. I bet it. But this is like right on the
freaking doorstep. This is a clear, clear threat. But what
about us having new? Yeah, you can't, you can't trust fucking
China, dude. They don't they're doing
I get what you're saying because that was my argument with
Iran. Who are we to tell anybody else not to have fucking
Enriching uranium. I'm just saying. Yeah, exactly. I mean, who are we? We're fucking America. That is speaking
I'm I'm gonna you're missing the point
You talk about nukes on a doorstep. Why is you're saying it's wrong for Russia to have it there, but where it's okay for us to
But it's not like missiles
Not to mention, we're the only country that's ever seen a hundred twenty-nits old bullies.